Okay, Spill, why would you ask me to come here, of all places?
Well, Fafnir?
Lend me your power.
What's this about?
Since when do you rely on others for anything besides gaming cheats or whatever?
Doesn't matter.
I know it doesn't seem like it, but I'm pretty busy.
You're just gonna have to ask someone else.
All right.
Hey, you're supposed to beg before walking away.
what's this for weird a manga what for and why there's a dojinshi exhibition coming up soon
and i plan to sell it there hold on you mean you're gonna draw it yourself the last time i
attempted a sale my book was text only and takia said that's why i was crushed royally
so i'm adding artwork here's what i don't get why are you so hard up to sell a book at this place
so badly because treasure uh what it was an ordinary day hey favkun you're a fan of treasure
aren't you sure how would you feel about creating it yourself then like diy treasure please elaborate
well when you create something yourself it becomes that much more valuable so imagine how much treasure
would be worth if you created it oh i see so you took that investment advice and made a book
is that why you want my power yes next time skip the flashbacks and just ask me okay of course i'd
love to help you so what do you want me to do blotting cross-hatching wow you know a lot but no
not that members of my online community say it's standard for books like these to feature erotic
and vulgar women so what i'm asking is that you model for my artwork
an art model i've never done that before wait rewind a second i'm pretty sure you use the term vulgar
is that how you see me undeniably i can't think of anyone better suited for the role you said that
right to my face here is the outline of the story uh this says that your main character is an
elementary school boy oh and a gorgeous older woman wait that's just like me and shota
stop what are you going to do to me i'm going to strip you naked and lick you all over it
no i won't let you escape
whoa what is this crap this woman is pure nightmare fuel i mean poor precious baby boy
you are correct but the main plot is coming up
okay so somehow they find a way to fall in love right damn that woman
but why why can't i stop thinking about her oh i know because i want to curse that woman to death
i'll curse that woman i'll curse her i hate her very existence i'll curse her i'll curse her
so uh fafnir lucoa all the pages after this one have the young boy casting endless curses
upon the beautiful woman yes that is the main focus of my vision
i don't think humans are going to understand your intention here at all right i need a rough draft
go ahead and try some poses okay got it
hmm that works
all right next i need poses for the curses
huh we're doing those too are you serious do you know of another reason why i would have bowed my head
i didn't see it fine how's this i'm in pain
what's going on are you mocking me i need to see bloodshot eyes in your neck twisted 360 degrees
since when you're my only hope no one else can pull it off so perfectly i'm not sure i like
that endorsement whatever here that's brilliant now spin your arms in irregular directions and then
try to fly with them broken oh sure now split your chest into three parts of course why wouldn't
hips arch your hips into a bridge and then climb down the stairs backwards
all in a day's work
excellent job
are you able to get the drawings you wanted
your thoughts
what's the matter why so distraught
hi fafgun i'm home
hey
oh hey what are you up to lukuwa
you know just hanging out
you're making another book i see
great is it good
of course
guess i better start getting my act together for the exhibition too
oh great last time he was there he sold out
i can't lose again
a book huh
that reminds me i haven't paid you for your work yet
help yourself to some of my treasure
you know what keep it i don't need any cursed treasures
better yet
i want to sell a book too
can i share some space at your booth
that's fine but what will you sell
hmm how about a book of some of my cosplay photos
you fool who would ever buy those
oh man this might be fun from time to time
can i have a copy of your book
since i helped out
no
i already shipped one to your home
huh
it's her
she's the vulgar devil
no way
i don't understand why she's like this
why
no
i refuse to let myself be tempted again and again
be gone demon
are you kidding me why did my love go off the way
oh that's right
she's like a warrior fresh from the battlefield
sunny days like this are my favorite for sleeping in
speaking of which do you ever get tired
not really dragons aren't prone to sleeping
fafnir stayed awake for thousands of years to protect his treasure
we find that sleep gets in the way of more important things
analog security how impressive
actually i do tend to get sleepy during the cold season
oh like hibernation
is that what you call it
at times i've fallen into a deep sleep and remain that way for most of the winter
and i usually can't wake up without a strong personal trigger
what triggers you
you know like the world suddenly becoming full of malice
or blood and miasma seeping into the earth and creating some foul and unbearable odor
so i guess a strong coffee is out of the question
i've noticed i am sleeping a lot more ever since living in this world with you
you're adapting to our lifestyle
that's part of it yeah
but strangely enough i want to sleep sometimes
there's a reason behind it too
speaking of sleeping a lot where's kana
over there snoozing
they have their own room i don't know why they don't just go to bed in there
neither of them were able to sleep with their parents in their world
so they're indulging in that here with you
i see
so was it different for you
yeah i guess so
i was pretty spoiled by my parents
all right
time for me to go back to sleep
wait let's go by yashii
jora please
this is my only joy
let me have it
she's impossible to wake up when she gets like that
oh well i guess i'll go shopping for dinner
i'm cursed with bad luck if i'm running into you
that's what i was gonna say
i know those bags are full of sweets
when did you stop being a dragon and become a swine
back off toru
i'm too tired and overwhelmed to process you right now
so does that mean you've started to sleep here too
it just started to come naturally to me
the more i learned about the way humans live
almost afraid to admit i've been sleeping every night since i came to this world
i assume you've been the same way
yeah
it's strange when you think about it
i mean where would this sleepiness come from
do you think it's a symptom of boredom
what are you saying
you're feeling bored
why don't you go back then
well because i don't dislike being bored
i mean think about how many years we had to fight our battles without actual sleep
when i compare that feeling to not having much to do throughout the day
i realize i actually enjoy the mindless leisure
don't you
toru
are we
whatever i wouldn't expect a pig like you to understand
i hope you get sold for at least 88 yen per 100 grams at a local butcher
how dare you suggest i've ever be sold so cheap
it's that time of night again
most humans are asleep and i can physically sense it
no matter where i look
i see the signs that confirm those feelings
it's not that i dislike this time of day
it's reassuring to know that so many humans are safely resting in their beds
it's so quiet
it is quiet
you want a nightcap
i slept too much this afternoon so yeah
guess i'm up for a bit
hey miss kobayashi i was wondering why do humans get sleepy
we need sleep to live
we'll die if we don't get it
for some reason we chose to be diurnal rather than nocturnal during our evolution
guess that's not what you were asking about huh
well maybe maybe it's pressure to conform
like just going along with what everyone wants to do
yeah
someone probably said it's getting dark out and we can't do anything anyway so let's just sleep
then someone else agreed
and so did their friends and their friends friends
and when everyone's asleep it's kind of lonely being awake by yourself
so everyone went to sleep together
or something like that
did i answer your question?
yeah
so then
that would mean i've also given in to the pressure
the pressure to conform
i fell asleep
today's gonna be a great day
good morning miss kobayashi
today you'll be investigating things in groups and we'll create a class newspaper
so let's have a discussion and decide what your theme will be
okay we should investigate ghosts
there have been rumors about that lately they say a woman's screams were heard from the art prep room
that might be interesting
ghosts
i like that idea too
i don't know if you want to
kind of don't say that there's no such thing as ghosts anyway
precisely how are we supposed to prove spirits exist when we can't see them
dude come on
ow that hurt
oh don't be dumb
you know what
you're kind of an egghead
you guys are all just afraid of ghosts
what
why would i be afraid of them
they're not even for real
truth
but i'm still willing to accompany you for our story
come with us too psycho
um arm twisted
i guess i could go with you but only to take care of kata
all right i guess that's settled
if a ghost shows up i'll show it what's what
ghosts don't have bodies so you can't show them
stop that
it's just a figure of speech
some people think ghosts show up in photos
are you gonna take some
if i caught one and posted it it would go viral
viral
viral that means it would get a lot of likes super fast
i like you
oh
let's take a photo of us three for now
rock paper scissors
all right
chocolate is good
bam
hey aren't we supposed to be investigating ghosts
we can take a break warden
i want to play too
for real
cool
let's start over so kuramoto can join in
no
i was just about to win
and the first person to reach the goal will be the leader of our group the leader's orders will be absolute which means psycho is a servant by default
what i'm a servant
you are such a pervert
huh you're so weird
let's do this kana we're gonna make these idiot creepers regret today
yay
rock paper scissors
go get em kana
chocolate is good
done
i did it first
looks like kana's the winner
that means anything she decides is absolute for all of us
time to give us your orders kana
what would you like
uh
hug me
are you sure
i'm so happy
she's been extra crazy lately
i can't be exposed to this
who wants to play some soccer
cut it out
what the heck is wrong with you hachiska
come on
we'll make a bet
boys versus girls
losers have to say the name of who they like
what
yeah right
that penalty wouldn't apply to me
i will only ever have eyes for my kana
have you ever wondered who kobayashi likes
let's get married shekua
hachiska you've made some good choices today
um thanks
all right let's get moving
i can't lose
this way
fair
why would you
listen i'll betray my team for you
that means i finally hear my sweet kata's proposal
looks like our plan worked
wow way to go kobayashi
what the crud
who made this stupid bucket fly at me
oh crap
strategic retreat
where'd they go
you're not getting away with this
not good
you think they saw our faces
i'm surprised you're such a wuss
shut up
stop it
that is too funny
you guys are so affected by older students
i want to play soccer some more
that was super fun
was that a scream from the art realm
yikes
is it
a ghost
um it's probably nothing
then why don't you check it out for us
why should i do it alone
we're all friends
we should do it together
whatever
you betrayed your friends earlier
you made me do it
i'll go check it out
okay
then i'll go with you
what's this
the sound was made by this window
told you
but you wouldn't listen
there's no such thing as ghosts you guys
i don't understand why you're so dumb
i was really hoping to take a photo of a ghost
what are we gonna do for the newspaper
we'll write a story about how the ghost in the art room is just a loose old window
what a boring story
yeah we need to write an article that's filled with thrills and suspense
big stuff up
creepy
come on kana we should go home
i apologize
it seems i've caused quite a stir
i seem to have been mistaken for a ghost
did you come here from another world
yes i suppose you could say that
though i ended up here by accident
what were you doing in the closet
i thought it was a good spot to avoid being seen by people
what was the sound
oh goodness
i was sharpening my nails on the blackboard
oh
by the by
i must give you snaps for blending in with the humans and living with them
really
indeed
humans are quite the mystery blocks of terror and highly unpredictable aren't they
they're not scary they're really fun
you sound like you enjoy them is that so
yeah i love them
well good for you
unfortunately i'm at quite a loss trying to find the way back to my world in my home
there is a way to get back to that world though i can help you
oh do you really mean that
this is so exhausting
i am eternally grateful to you
this is a kindness i will never forget
no way
check this out our next investigation is space
what after dragging us all over the place on a wild ghost chase
aliens are different though they exist
if they look good in photos i'm sold
i can't go along with this anymore
sounds like fun
i'll do it
kana can we talk
so now that that's settled we can meet after school
and investigate the city
what fine i'll come along with you
then you have to carry all of our stuff for joining
wait
uh no i don't
i'll carry kana's stuff but the rest of you maggots are on your own
Hey, Kana.
What did you decide to write about for your class newspaper?
Outer space.
I like that. It's romantic.
We're gonna start with the Roswell incident in Area 51.
Wow, we're actually going there, huh?
This week on Who's Rotten?
Aquarius.